Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Campaign Office Files Record Group, 1982-1997 and undated
  - 1988 Campaign Series, 14 boxes
    - Election Returns (Box ACA-19)
      - 1986 General Election (Box ACA-19)
      - Primary 1988-Randolph County, Chatham County (Box ACA-19)
    - Fetzer Clips (Box ACA-19)
    - Sample Ballots (Box ACA-19)
    - Palm Card (Box ACA-19)
    - Highlights Card and David Price Flyer (Box ACA-19)
    - Kick-off Card (Box ACA-19)
    - Print Ads (Box ACA-20)
    - [Campaign Literature] (Box ACA-20)
    - Wake County Tabloid (Box ACA-20)
    - Non-Wake Tabloid (Box ACA-20)
    - Ballot Card (Box ACA-20)
    - Emergency Ballot Flyer (Election Day) (Box ACA-20)
    - Ballot Flyer-Club (Box ACA-20)
    - Petty Cash Reports, 1988 (Box ACA-20)
    - Raleigh Office Receipts (Box ACA-20)
    - Interns, etc. (Box ACA-20)
    - RTP/Cappers (Box ACA-20)
    - Glenn/Towns (Box ACA-20)
    - Benson/Gailor (Box ACA-20)
    - Bland/Carr (Box ACA-20)
    - Duke/Bradley (Box ACA-20)
    - Ayr Mount (Box ACA-20)
    - Monteith/Owens (Box ACA-20)
    - Indians/Horwitz (Box ACA-20)
    - Angus Barn/Daniels (Box ACA-20)
    - Invites to Meet, etc. (Box ACA-20)
    - Invitations (Box ACA-21)
    - Mailings '88 (Box ACA-21)
    - Kickoff Speech (Box ACA-21)
    - Special Interest Groups '88 (Box ACA-21)
    - Siler City-Jerry Wood (Box ACA-21)
    - [Miscellaneous], 2 folders (Box ACA-21)
    - Finance Call (Box ACA-21)
    - FEC Report, 2 folders (Box ACA-21)
    - [Miscellaneous], 2 folders (Box ACA-21)
    - Angus Barn Event (Box ACA-21)
    - Daniels Event (Box ACA-21)
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box ACA-21)
    - Lists (Box ACA-21)
    - Christie B., R-11 Samples (Box ACA-21)
    - 1988 Final Thank You (Box ACA-22)
    - Christie B., R-12 Samples (Box ACA-22)
    - Resolicitation-R 4, 5, 6 (Box ACA-22)
    - Prospecting-PR 2, 3, 4 (Box ACA-22)
    - Printouts (Box ACA-22)
    - Angus Barn, 1988 June 6 (Box ACA-22)
    - Daniels Event, 1988 Aug. 1 (Box ACA-22)
    - Bland (Box ACA-22)
    - Carr, 1988 Oct. 16 (Box ACA-22)
    - [Morehead Alumni] (Box ACA-22)
    - Horwitz-Jewish (Box ACA-22)
    - Glenn/Bankers, 1988 Nov. 1 (Box ACA-22)
    - Duke Event, 1988 Sept. 19, 2 folders (Box ACA-22)
    - Duke Fundraiser (Box ACA-22)
    - Gailor (Box ACA-22)
    - Major Donor #2 (Box ACA-22)
    - Duke List (Box ACA-22)
    - FEC Report, 2 folders (Box ACA-23)
    - Duke/Durham Lists (Box ACA-23)
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box ACA-23)
    - [Project on International Child Research and Policy] (Box ACA-23)
    - Bulk Mail Account (Box ACA-23)
    - CPA/Anthony Event (Box ACA-23)
    - Chicago Fundraisers, Linda Davis, May 13-14 (Box ACA-23)
    - Congressional Mailings (Box ACA-23)
    - Congressional Quarterly (Box ACA-23)
    - Correspondence (Box ACA-23)
    - County Totals-$, 1986 (Box ACA-23)
    - Davis, Linda (Box ACA-23)
    - Democratic Party (Box ACA-23)
    - Doctors' Fundraiser-Freedman Home, 2 folders (Box ACA-23)
    - FEC (Box ACA-23)
    - Finance Group (Box ACA-23)
    - Foley Event-Golf Tourney, 1987 Sept. 26 (Box ACA-23)
    - Fuquay BBQ-Ed Jones (Box ACA-23)
    - Hyde, Luke-Page, Gray, and Laughinghouse, Apr. 24 (Box ACA-23)
    - Invoices-Bills (Box ACA-23)
    - Issues (Box ACA-23)
    - Lawyers' Reception, Apr. 18 (Box ACA-24)
    - Major Donor Letter, 1988 Apr. 22 (Box ACA-24)
    - McMillen Event (Box ACA-24)
    - Millers (Howard and Judy) (Box ACA-24)
    - Nurses' Reception (Box ACA-24)
    - Orange County (Box ACA-24)
    - PACs (Box ACA-24)
    - Pending (Box ACA-24)
    - Precinct Official Letter-PR 2, 1988 May (Box ACA-24)
    - Press Releases (Box ACA-24)
    - Printers (Box ACA-24)
    - Prospects (Box ACA-24)
    - Prospect Letter #4 (Hunt Letter), 1988 July (Box ACA-24)
    - Questionnaires (Box ACA-24)
    - T. K. Rao-Small Business (Box ACA-24)
    - Rashkis Event (Box ACA-24)
    - Randolph Fundraiser-Luria (Box ACA-24)
    - Realtors (Box ACA-24)
    - Research Triangle Fundraiser (Box ACA-24)
    - Resolicitation #4, Mar. 16 (Box ACA-24)
    - Resolicitation #5, 1988 May (Box ACA-24)
    - R6-Samples (Box ACA-24)
    - Resolicitation #8 (Box ACA-24)
    - Resolicitation #10 (Box ACA-24)
    - Sandhu Event (Box ACA-24)
    - Sample Invites (Box ACA-24)
    - Schmalbeck Event (Box ACA-24)
    - St. Augustine Fundraiser, July 11 (Box ACA-24)
    - St. Augustine Fundraiser, July 11 (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
    - Strategy Group (Box ACA-24)
    - Telephone (Box ACA-24)
    - Trash (Box ACA-24)
    - Letters to Editor: Pro-Price Return File (Box ACA-25)
    - TV Ads-Press (Box ACA-25)
    - Election Week Press (Box ACA-25)
    - Newspaper Ads, Information (Box ACA-25)
    - Wake County Mayor's Endorsements (Box ACA-25)
    - Debate Press (Box ACA-25)
    - Orange County Tabloid (Box ACA-25)
    - Franklin County Mayoral Endorsements (Box ACA-25)
    - Miscellaneous Endorsements by Organizations (Box ACA-25)
    - County Chairs, Press Memo to ... (Box ACA-25)
    - Press Conference Strategy-Humphrey Memo (Box ACA-25)
    - ANA-PAC [American Nursing Association], News Release Statement (Box ACA-25)
    - BPW [Business and Professional Women] Endorsement (and Forum) and Press Release, 1988 (Box ACA-25)
    - NCAE [North Carolina Association of Educators]-Press Releases and Coverage Re: Endorsement (Box ACA-25)
    - Senator Bradley Visit (Box ACA-25)
    - Etheridge/Price Press Conference (Box ACA-25)
    - Foley, Congressman Tom-Visit (Box ACA-25)
    - Glenn, John (Box ACA-25)
    - Glenn, Senator John-Luncheon (Box ACA-25)
    - Lewis, John-Visit (Box ACA-25)
    - Townes Visit (Congressman Ed Townes), 1988 Oct. 29 (Box ACA-25)
    - Endorsements-Press, 1986 (Box ACA-25)
    - [Unlabeled folder], 2 folders (Box ACA-25)
    - Candidate Profiles (Price and Fetzer) (Box ACA-25)
    - Capitol Hill Activity: Newsletters, Reports (Box ACA-25)
    - Community Meetings and Congressional Appearances (Box ACA-25)
    - Democratic Party/Election Press Featuring David Price (Box ACA-25)
    - Dome Clips (Box ACA-25)
    - Editorials and Cartoons (Box ACA-25)
    - Endorsements From Newspapers (Box ACA-25)
    - Financial Press (Box ACA-25)
    - Filing for Reelection-Press (Box ACA-25)
    - 4th District Day Press (Box ACA-25)
    - Letters to Editor (anti-Price) (Box ACA-25)
    - General (Race)-Not Price/Fetzer Exclusive (Box ACA-25)
    - Price/Fetzer Specific (Race) (Box ACA-25)
    - N.C. Issues/Concerns (Box ACA-25)
    - N.C. Economic Indicators (Box ACA-25)
    - North Carolina Agriculture (Box ACA-25)
    - RDU International Airport (Box ACA-26)
    - Media List (Box ACA-26)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings
      - Carolinian (Box ACA-26)
      - Chapel Hill Herald (Box ACA-26)
      - Cary News (Box ACA-26)
      - Courier-Tribune (Box ACA-26)
      - Daily Tar Heel (Box ACA-26)
      - Garner News (Box ACA-26)
      - Franklin Times (Box ACA-26)
      - Wake Weekly (Box ACA-26)
      - Western Wake Herald (Box ACA-26)
      - Zebulon Record (Box ACA-26)
    - Appearances for Fetzer (Box ACA-26)
    - Fetzer's "Bio" of David (Box ACA-26)
    - Biography of Fetzer (Box ACA-26)
    - Fetzer-generated Press (Miscellaneous) (Box ACA-26)
    - Fetzer Miscellaneous Press (Box ACA-26)
    - Biographies-Price, 1988 (Box ACA-26)
    - Democratic Women (Box ACA-26)
    - Democratic Congressional Convention Speech (Box ACA-26)
    - Speech to Democratic National Convention, 1988 July 21 (Box ACA-26)
    - WPTF Radio "In Touch" Interviews with Price and Fetzer, 1988 Oct. (Box ACA-26)
    - Kick Off Speech (Box ACA-26)
    - Kick Off Day Press Pack, 1988 (Box ACA-26)
    - Kick Off Press Coverage (Box ACA-26)
    - Kick Off Day Preparation (Box ACA-26)
    - Republican Political Ads '88 (Paid Advertising) (Box ACA-26)
    - Transcripts of Spots (Paid Advertising) (Box ACA-26)
    - Ballot Controversy Coverage (Box ACA-26)
    - B'nai B'rith, 1988 Sept. 26 (Box ACA-26)
    - Budget/Deficit Press (Box ACA-26)
    - Burnley/RDU Controversy (Box ACA-26)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1989 Sept. 20 (Box ACA-26)
    - Child Care (Box ACA-26)
    - Franklin County Airport, 1988 Oct. 6 (Box ACA-26)
    - Home Builders' Association Forum (Box ACA-26)
    - Home Equity (Final Days) (Box ACA-26)
    - Literacy Press (Box ACA-26)
    - McCollum Amendment Press (Box ACA-26)
    - McCollum Amendment Letters (Box ACA-26)
    - Pledge of Allegiance (Box ACA-26)
    - Post Office Articles/Letters (Box ACA-26)
    - Tax Vote/Burnley Press Conference (Box ACA-26)
    - Veterans Center Press (Box ACA-27)
    - [Miscellaneous Printed Materials] (Box ACA-27)
    - Congressional Club Connection Press (Box ACA-27)
    - Campaign 1988 (Box ACA-27)
    - Receipts and Disbursements (Box ACA-27)
    - Fetzer FEC, 1988 July 1-Oct. 19 (Box ACA-27)
    - Price Campaign 1988-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box ACA-27)
    - Budget-Price Statements, Pre-Campaign (Box ACA-27)
    - 1988 Questionnaires
      - Economy (Box ACA-27)
      - Opening Statement (Box ACA-27)
      - Local Activities (Box ACA-27)
      - Legislative Initiatives (Box ACA-27)
      - Veterans (Box ACA-27)
    - Budget (Box ACA-27)
    - Committee: This Week (Box ACA-27)
    - Donor Listing (Box ACA-27)
    - Press Kit (Box ACA-27)
  - 1990 Campaign Series, 3 boxes
    - Angus Barn Fundraiser (Box ACA-28)
    - Fundraising-Events (Box ACA-28)
    - Filing, Primary/Clips (Box ACA-28)
    - GOP-Miscellaneous (Box ACA-28)
    - DP-Group Ratings/Program Support (Box ACA-28)
    - Homebuilders Association (Box ACA-28)
    - Legislative Resume (Box ACA-28)
    - Letters to the Editor (Box ACA-28)
    - Middle East (Carrington and Price) (Box ACA-28)
    - NARAL [National Abortion Rights Action League] (Box ACA-28)
    - NCAE [North Carolina Association of Educators] (Box ACA-28)
    - NCEC [National Committee for an Effective Congress] Project (Box ACA-28)
    - Price Record-PR/PC (Box ACA-28)
    - Profile Articles-DP Campaign (Box ACA-28)
    - 1990 Questionnaires (Box ACA-28)
    - Sheriffs' Endorsements (Box ACA-28)
    - Sierra Club PC, 1990 Oct. 24 (Box ACA-28)
    - 'Groups' for Price (Box ACA-28)
    - Wake Mayor's Endorsement (Box ACA-28)
    - WFMY Forum, 1990 Oct. 30 (Box ACA-28)
    - WUNC-TV Interview, 1990 Sept. 24 (Box ACA-28)
    - MAC [i.e., Mac McCorkle), 5 folders (Box ACA-28)
    - Kickoff Packet Originals (Box ACA-29)
    - N.C. Veterans News Ad (Box ACA-29)
    - Newspaper Ads-Dailies (Box ACA-29)
    - Schedule Advisories (Box ACA-29)
    - Price on the Issues (Box ACA-29)
    - Franking (Box ACA-29)
    - Carrington
      - FEC Reports (Box ACA-29)
      - Human Rights (Box ACA-29)
      - And the GOP/Helms (Box ACA-29)
      - Media Buys-Radio (Box ACA-29)
      - Media Buys-TV (Box ACA-29)
      - Negatives-Responses (Box ACA-29)
      - PACs (Box ACA-29)
      - Poison Pen Letters (Box ACA-29)
      - Print Ads (Box ACA-29)
      - Printed Material (Box ACA-29)
      - Research (Box ACA-29)
      - St L's (Box ACA-29)
      - TV/Radio Ads (Box ACA-29)
      - Term Limitation (Box ACA-29)
      - Wright/Coehlo (Box ACA-29)
    - Print Material
      - Accomplishment Card (Box ACA-29)
      - CH "Price Difference" Piece (Box ACA-29)
      - Fowler Ads, Chapel Hill News and Chapel Hill Herald (Box ACA-29)
      - "Fact Sheets" (Box ACA-29)
      - Orange County Voter Tab (Box ACA-29)
      - "Re-Elect David Price" (Box ACA-29)
      - "Super Keys" Newsletter (Box ACA-29)
      - Co. Keys-Letters to Editor (Box ACA-29)
      - State Employee Reporter Ad (Box ACA-29)
      - Raleigh Issue Pieces (Box ACA-29)
      - Palm Cards (Box ACA-29)
    - Mailings
      - Price Kickoff (Box ACA-29)
      - Volunteer Letters (Box ACA-29)
      - Campaign Bio (Box ACA-29)
      - North Raleigh Living Ads (Box ACA-29)
    - Price Campaign/Press
      - Tabloid (Box ACA-29)
      - Weekly Ads (Box ACA-29)
    - Carrington (Box ACA-30)
      - Biography (Box ACA-30)
      - Budget (Box ACA-30)
      - Campaign Staff (Box ACA-30)
      - Campaign Stops/Appearances (Box ACA-30)
      - DP Congressional Staff (Box ACA-30)
      - Direct Mail (Box ACA-30)
      - Editorials (Box ACA-30)
      - Endorsements (Box ACA-30)
      - Environment (Box ACA-30)
    - Environment (Box ACA-30)
    - FEC Reports-DP (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Spending-DP (Box ACA-30)
    - Carrington-Ethics/Pay Raise (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
    - Campaign Spending-PACs (DP) (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Newsletters (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Spending Plan-DP/JC Comments and Responses (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Spending Plan-Clips (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Spending Original Letters (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Spending-PACs General (Box ACA-30)
    - Campaign Stops (Miscellaneous) (Box ACA-30)
    - Co-chair Press Releases (Box ACA-30)
    - Clips-Congressional-Miscellaneous (Box ACA-30)
    - Clips-Miscellaneous Political (DP) (Box ACA-30)
    - Clips-Miscellaneous Political (General) (Box ACA-30)
    - DCCC Incumbent Workshop, 1990 May 4-5, 2 folders (Box ACA-30)
    - Debates (Box ACA-30)
    - Direct Mail-Miscellaneous (Box ACA-30)
    - Editorials (Box ACA-30)
    - Election Night Speech (Box ACA-30)
    - Election Returns/Coverage (Box ACA-30)
    - Endorsements, 1990 (Box ACA-30)
    - Endorsement-Franklin Mayoral (Box ACA-30)
    - Fundraising-DP/JC (Box ACA-30)
    - Other counties (Box ACA-30)
    - PFC Phones per P.R. (Box ACA-30)
  - 1994 Campaign Series, 2 boxes
    - Targeted Mail (Box ACA-31)
    - Fred Heineman (Box ACA-31)
    - 1994 Statement of Candidacy (Box ACA-31)
    - Angus Barn, 1994 (Box ACA-31)
    - Campaign Speeches (Box ACA-31)
    - Campaign Budget (Box ACA-31)
    - Consultant: Shorr (Box ACA-31)
    - Contributions, 1994 (Box ACA-31)
    - DCCC [Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee] (Box ACA-31)
    - [Victory '94 Coordinated Campaign Plan] (Box ACA-31)
    - Articles and Politics, 1994 (Box ACA-31)
    - 1994 Campaign Accounting (Box ACA-31)
    - Charlotte Trip (Box ACA-31)
    - Davis/Klein DC Fundraiser (Box ACA-31)
    - Endorsements (Box ACA-31)
    - FEC Report, 1994 Jan. 31 (Box ACA-31)
    - FEC Report, 1994 July 15 (Box ACA-31)
    - Fundraising (Box ACA-31)
    - Filing Documents, 1994 (Box ACA-31)
    - Friends (Box ACA-31)
    - Heineman FEC Report, 1994 July 15 (Box ACA-31)
    - Campaign/FEC Rules (Box ACA-32)
    - Polls (Box ACA-32)
    - FEC Report, Sept. 30 (Box ACA-32)
    - Spending Limits (Box ACA-32)
    - Rob Romaine (Box ACA-32)
  - 1996 Campaign Series, 7 boxes
    - Issues (Box ACA-33)
      - DCCC [Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee] Research Division, Research Report on Fred Heineman (NC-04), 1996 Apr. (Box ACA-33)
      - Price Legislative Record, 1987-1990 (Box ACA-33)
      - Researching-DCCC (Box ACA-33)
      - DCCC Voting Database (Box ACA-33)
      - Press List (Box ACA-33)
      - Good Enviro. Commercial Backup (Box ACA-33)
      - National Taxpayers Union (Box ACA-33)
      - DP Key Votes (Box ACA-33)
      - "Reports from Washington" Newsletter (Box ACA-33)
      - DP-1996 Endorsements (Box ACA-33)
      - The Basics (Box ACA-33)
      - Peacock/Carolina (Box ACA-33)
      - N.C. State/UNC Education Letter (Box ACA-33)
      - Editorials About David (Box ACA-33)
      - David's Votes with Democratic Congress, 100th-103rd (Box ACA-33)
      - David's Congressional Book (Box ACA-33)
      - Masonboro Incident (Box ACA-33)
      - David's Essays/Articles (Box ACA-34)
      - Campaign-Republican Pact [Contract With America], 1994 Sept. 23 (Box ACA-34)
      - Contract With America/Freshman Republicans (Box ACA-34)
      - Ad Copy (Box ACA-34)
      - House Banking Issues (Box ACA-34)
      - DP Personal-Pay Raises (Box ACA-34)
      - DP and DC Prison Attack (Box ACA-34)
      - FH's [Fred Heineman's] Crime Ad (Box ACA-34)
      - Attacks on DP (Box ACA-34)
      - FH's TV Buys (Box ACA-34)
      - Radio Commercials (Box ACA-34)
      - FH's Negative Medicare Ad (Box ACA-34)
      - TV Directions, Shorr Records (Box ACA-34)
      - 1994 FH Campaign Ads (Box ACA-34)
      - Web Site Stuff (Box ACA-34)
      - Letters to the Editor (Box ACA-34)
      - Quotes Database (Box ACA-34)
      - Door Hanger Background (Box ACA-35)
      - Fred and Newt (Box ACA-35)
      - Correspondence w/FH, 1996 (Box ACA-35)
      - General Articles about FH (Box ACA-35)
      - Debates, 1994 Election (Box ACA-35)
      - Heineman and DP PAC Analysis (Box ACA-35)
      - FH and the Journal (Box ACA-35)
      - Heineman's Medicare Propaganda (Box ACA-35)
      - Fred's Newsletters (Box ACA-35)
      - FH and the General Election, 1994 (Box ACA-35)
      - Clean Campaign, 1994 (Box ACA-35)
      - 1994 Endorsements (Box ACA-35)
      - PACs/Fundraising, 1996 Election (Box ACA-35)
      - 1996 Kickoff-Filing Speech, DP (Box ACA-35)
      - DP/FH Transition Controversy (Box ACA-35)
      - General about the District/Voters, 1996 Election (Box ACA-35)
      - Medicare Cuts-FH and Budget (Box ACA-35)
      - "Middle Class"-FH and Budget (Box ACA-35)
      - Median Income Stuff (Box ACA-35)
      - Breakdown of Rep. Tax Cut (Box ACA-35)
      - FH and Police Budget (Box ACA-35)
      - Government Shutdown (Box ACA-35)
      - 1994 Election-DP and Budget (Box ACA-35)
      - More Veterans (Box ACA-35)
      - Franking (Box ACA-35)
      - Medicare Analysis (Box ACA-35)
      - EPA / North Raleigh Living Article (Box ACA-35)
      - Community Policing (Box ACA-36)
      - General Environment-FH and Environment (Box ACA-36)
      - General Crime-FH and Crime (Box ACA-36)
      - Cop Killer Bullets-FH and Crime (Box ACA-36)
      - Waco Hearings-FH and Crime (Box ACA-36)
      - Washington D.C. Crime Proposal-FH and Crime (Box ACA-36)
      - DP and Crime, 1994 Election (Box ACA-36)
      - DP: SandL (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
    - Anti-Drug Program-FH Press Release (Box ACA-36)
    - Provide Rides to the Polls (Box ACA-36)
    - Kickoff Letter (Box ACA-36)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box ACA-36)
    - Other Groups' Literature (Box ACA-36)
    - Sierra Club (Box ACA-36)
    - Others on WRAL-5 TV (Box ACA-36)
    - Police Benevolent Association (Box ACA-36)
    - Retired Officers Association (Box ACA-36)
    - RESULTS and Microcredit Summit (Box ACA-36)
    - The Savings Coalition-IRAs (Box ACA-36)
    - Labor Unions (Box ACA-36)
    - NARFE [National Association of Retired Federal Employees] Information (Box ACA-37)
    - National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare (Box ACA-37)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens (Box ACA-37)
    - New Democrat Network (Box ACA-37)
    - JACPAC [Joint Action Committee for Political Affairs] (Box ACA-37)
    - Ratings from Outside Groups (Box ACA-37)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, Inc. (Box ACA-37)
    - Christian Coalition (Box ACA-37)
    - Citizens for the Republic (Box ACA-37)
    - Citizen Action (Box ACA-37)
    - Democrats 2000 (Box ACA-37)
    - Fight Crime: Invest in Kids (Box ACA-37)
    - Interfaith Alliance (Box ACA-37)
    - League of Conservation Voters (Box ACA-37)
    - Interest Group Ratings (Box ACA-37)
    - Direct Mail Letter I (Box ACA-37)
    - Direct Mail Vendors (Box ACA-38)
    - Labor (Box ACA-38)
    - Price Difference (Box ACA-38)
    - Wake County Democrats and Keynote Speech (Box ACA-38)
    - Abortion (Box ACA-38)
    - Appropriations Comparison (DP to FH) (Box ACA-38)
    - Assault Weapon Ban (Box ACA-38)
    - DCCC Rhetoric (Box ACA-38)
    - Clinton Economic Plan Defense (Box ACA-38)
    - Crime (Box ACA-38)
    - Database Codes and Reports (Box ACA-38)
    - Katie McGinty/Wake Enviro. Event (Box ACA-38)
    - Government Shutdown (Box ACA-38)
    - Heineman AFL-CIO Letter (Box ACA-38)
    - Journal Vote (Box ACA-38)
    - Kimberly Summaries (Box ACA-38)
    - Laborers (Box ACA-38)
    - Minimum Wage (Box ACA-38)
    - Names/Messages (Box ACA-38)
    - North Raleigh Living Article (Box ACA-38)
    - Record Contrasts (Box ACA-38)
    - Republican Independent Expenditure (Box ACA-38)
    - RNC Funded Ad (Box ACA-38)
    - Third Party Heineman Flyers (Box ACA-38)
    - Heineman Record-DCCC Research (Box ACA-38)
    - Accounting Fees (Box ACA-38)
    - Peace PAC (Box ACA-38)
    - Orange County/Heffner (Box ACA-38)
    - Concord Coalition Debate (Box ACA-38)
    - Chatham County Committee (Box ACA-38)
    - Veterans' Breakfast (Box ACA-38)
    - Scheduling Request Forms (Box ACA-38)
    - Tim Thompkins, 1994 Election Notes (Box ACA-39)
    - The Price Record: 1987-1990 (Box ACA-39)
    - Original Copy-Forms (Box ACA-39)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress (NCEC) (Box ACA-39)
    - Television spots (Box ACA-39)
    - TV buy (Box ACA-39)
    - A-B event names (Box ACA-39)
    - Miscellaneous (Box ACA-39)
    - DNC Campaign Training Manuals (Box ACA-39)
    - Personal notes/DP (positive), 2 folders (Box ACA-39)
    - Precinct Targeting and Electoral Analysis (Box ACA-39)
  - Various Campaigns Series, 1986-1998 and undated, 8 boxes
    Materials in this subseries originated during a variety of campaigns but center primarily on those of the 1990s, especially 1992 and 1994. Original order has been retained.
    - Gene, 2 folders (Box ACA-40)
    - Campaign, 1989, 2 folders (Box ACA-40)
    - Price Newsletter, 1989 Mar. (Box ACA-40)
    - Windley, Bill (Box ACA-40)
    - Hansen, Annie Lee (Box ACA-40)
    - Staff Good Letters/Thank You's (Box ACA-40)
    - Paxton, Nancy (Box ACA-40)
    - Price Votes (Box ACA-40)
    - Price Legislation (Box ACA-40)
    - MacGregor Downs (Box ACA-40)
    - North Carolina. Governor (1985-1993: Martin) (Box ACA-40)
    - D.P. Book (Box ACA-40)
    - SERO [Southeastern Region Office, Nationwide Insurance Companies] Messenger (Box ACA-40)
    - Statement-filing for re-election, 1994 Jan. 19 (Box ACA-40)
    - Speech-Filing, 1992 Feb. 28 (Box ACA-40)
    - Book Material-DP Articles (Box ACA-40)
    - Clippings, 1 of 4 folders (Box ACA-40)
    - Clippings, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: People's Alliance (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Power in Citizenship (Box ACA-41)
    - REA [Research and Education Association] Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: SANE (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Triangle Business (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: U.S. Defense Committee (Box ACA-41)
    - The Price Difference (Box ACA-41)
    - Friends Committee Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Mentally Ill Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - North Carolina Association of Federal Employees (Retired) Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Reverend Kent Kelly (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: NCCLU [North Carolina Civil Liberties Union] (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Peace PAC (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: North Carolina League of Savings Institutions (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Orange County Green Coalition (Box ACA-41)
    - League of Conservation Voters Questionnaire 1990 (Box ACA-41)
    - North Carolina Dietetic Association Questionnaire 1990 (Box ACA-41)
    - PTA Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Child Care Networks Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Enact/PAC Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Freedom Council (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Full Employment Action Council (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: Gun Owners of America (Box ACA-41)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation of North Carolina Questionnaire (Box ACA-41)
    - League of Conservation Voters (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: NEA [National Education Association] (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaire: League of Women Voters (Box ACA-41)
    - Questionnaires: Campaigns (Box ACA-41)
    - McCorkle Memos (Box ACA-42)
    - Mac Campaign Memo, 1989 May 30 (Box ACA-42)
    - McCorkle and miscellaneous memos, 1986-1988 (Box ACA-42)
    - Mac Message, 1997 (Box ACA-42)
    - Carrington Poll, 1989 (Box ACA-42)